A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Special Collections, Grant Funded Materials FA1839
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grant File Attachments - Publications and Reports, 1955-2018; 5; 23.46 Cubic Feet
  - PA#8750398 - La Situacion Poblacionel Peruana, Balance y Perspectivas published by Alberto Varillas Montenegro and Patricia Mostajo de Muente, Andean Institute for Population Studies and Development, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 88)
    Grant Dates: 1987 March 02-1990 June 30
    Grant Number: 08750398
    Grant Purpose: Support for preparation of a national population-status report on Peru
    Ford Program Officer(s): Munoz-Najar, Antonio
  - PA#8751003 - Clientelismo: El Sistema Politico y su Expresion Regional by Francisco Leal Buitrago and Andres Davila Ladron de Guevara, National University of Colombia, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 89)
    Grantee: National University of Colombia
    Grant Dates: 1987 September 01-1989 June 30
    Grant Number: 08751003
    Grant Purpose: Support a new program of research on social violence and political reform
    Grant Amount: $50,000.00; $50,000.00
    Ford Program Officer(s): De la Flor, Pablo
  - PA#9000565 - Politicos y Militares by Maria Teresa Covarrubias, Center for Socio-Economic Studies of Development, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 90)
    Grantee: Center for Socio-Economic Studies of Development
    Grant Dates: 09000565
    Grant Number: 1990 January 15-1991 August 31
    Grant Purpose: Research, seminars, training and dialogue between civilians and the military in Chile
    Grant Amount: $80,000.00; $80,000.00
  - PA#9000565 - Cual Debe Ser el Gasto Militar en el Chile de los 90? by Guillermo Pattillo, Fernando Bustamante, and Miguel Navarro, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 91)
  - PA#8450957 - Contadora: Desafio a la Diplomacia Tradicional by Fernando Cepeda Ulloa and Rodrigo Pardo Garcia-Pena, University of the Andes, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 92)
    Grantee: University of the Andes
    Grant Dates: 1985 January 01-1986 January 31
    Grant Number: 08450957
    Grant Purpose: Preparation of six case studies of international negotiations conducted by the colombian public sector
    Ford Program Officer(s): Cox, Stephen B.
  - Queen Elizabeth House, Oxford University Refugee Studies Programme PA 09000140, 1990-1998 (Box 13, Folder 107, Box 14, Folder 108)
    Grantee: Queen Elizabeth House(UK)
    Grant Dates: 1989 October 01-1997 December 31
    Grant Number: 09000140
    Grant Purpose: Support for the core activities of the Refugee Studies Programme
    Grant Amount: $1,100,000.00; $1,100,000.00
    Ford Program Officers: Forman, Shepard; Higashi, Taryn
  - Consumers Union PA 09701083, 2004-2005 (Box 14, Folder 109)
    Grantee: Consumers Union of United States, Inc.
    Grant Dates: 2008 October 01-2010 September 30 Grant Number: 09701083
    Grant Purpose: Partial support for project to preserve charitable resources in the conversion of nonprofit institutions to for-profit corporations
    Grant Amount: $1,000,000.00; $1,000,000.00
    Ford Program Officer(s): Harris, Christopher; Edwards, Michael
  - Manpower Demonstration Research Corporation (MDRC) PA 09800884, 2005-2006 (Box 14, Folder 110)
    Grantee: Manpower Demonstration Research Corporation (MDRC)
    Grant Dates: 1998 January 01-2006 August 31
    Grant Number: 09800884
    Grant Purpose: Initial support for the evaluation of Project GRAD's replication in Newark
    Grant Amount: $3,700,200.00; $3,700,200.00
    Ford Program Officer(s): Zwerling, L. Steven; Petrovich, Janice
  - Women's Learning Partnership (WLP) PA 10101227, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 111)
    Grantee: Women's Learning Partnership for Rights, Development, and Peace
    Grant Dates: 2001 May 01-2011 June 30
    Grant Number: (10101227)
    Grant Purpose: For the Partnership's Cyber Institute to create culture-specific, multimedia education tools for individuals and organizations supporting Muslim women's participation and leadership
    Grant Amount: $975,000.00; $975,000.00
    Ford Program Officer(s): Phillips, Barbara; Silliman, Jael Miriam
  - University of the Philippines PA 10251806, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 112-113)
    Grantee: University of the Philippines
    Grant Dates: (10251806)
    Grant Number: 2002 September 01-2005 August 31
    Grant Purpose: To fully integrate the Reproductive Health, Rights and Ethics Center for Studies and Training into the College of Medicine
    Grant Amount: $177,000.00; $177,000.00
    Ford Program Officer(s): Tharan, Caridad T. Sri
  - National Council for Research on Women PA 09700130, 1996-1999 (Box 15, Folder 114, Box 16, Folder 115)
    Grantee: National Council for Research on Women
    Grant Dates: 1996 September 01-2008 April 30
    Grant Number: (09700130)
    Grant Purpose: Core support
    Grant Amount: $2,400,000.00; $2,400,000.00
    Ford Program Officer(s): Petrovich, Janice; Fraser, Gertrude Jacinta
  - Emprender Microenterprise Savings & Loan - $1,000,000 Recoverable Grant Agreement Between The Ford Foundation and Emprender PA 10001672, 2001 October 3 (Box 16, Folder 116)
    Grantee: Microenterprise Savings and Loan Cooperative of Colombia (EMPRENDER)
    Grant Dates: 2001 July 01-2011 June 30
    Grant Number: 10001672
    Grant Purpose: Recoverable grant to increase funds available to members, strengthen network income-generating services, expand microcredit learning, and increase credit for the disadvantaged in Colombia
    Ford Program Officer(s): DeGiovanni, Frank F.; Lacoste, Jean Paul; Tillett, Anthony D.
  - University of the Philippines PA 10251806, 2005-2006 (Box 16, Folder 117-118)
    Grant Dates: 2002 September 01-2005 August 31 Archival Object
    Grant Number: 10251806
  - President and Fellows of Harvard College PA 09901022, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 119, Box 17, Folder 120)
    Grantee: Harvard University
    Grant Dates: 1999 July 01-2004 June 30
    Grant Number: 09901022
    Grant Purpose: Support for the Harvard Trade Union Program's "Labor Leaders International Forum"
    Grant Amount: $629,000.00; $629,000.00
    Ford Program Officer(s): Jenkins, Alan
  - The Radio and Television News Directors Foundation - Newsroom Ethics, News Decision-Making Workshop PA 09801267, 2001 April 6-7 (Box 17, Folder 121)
    Grantee: Radio Television News Directors Foundation
    Grant Dates: 1998 May 01-2005 September 14
    Grant Number: 09801267
    Grant Purpose: For training workshops, public discussions, research and publications to promote improved ethical practices by broadcast news journalists
    Grant Amount: $1,600,000.00; $1,600,000.00
    Ford Program Officer(s): Funabiki, Jon
  - Israel Movement for Progressive Judaism PA 09700689, 1998-2001 (Box 17, Folder 122)
    Grantee: Israeli Movement for Progressive Judaism
    Grant Dates: 1997 March 01-2005 March 31
    Grant Number: 09700689
    Grant Purpose: Support for the activities of the Israel Religious Action Center to advance religious freedom And pluralism in Israel
    Grant Amount: $560,000.00; $560,000.00
    Ford Program Officer(s): Back, Aaron I.; Buchanan, Constance H.
  - Trustees of Columbia University - Sustainable Development and Environmental Economics Task Force PA 10200276, 2005 June 20 (Box 18, Folder 123-124)
    Grantee: The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York
    Grant Dates: 2001 November 01-2006 December 31
    Grant Number: 10200276
    Grant Purpose: For research and to organize task forces to assist developing countries in designing economic reform programs
    Grant Amount: $1,241,000.00; $1,241,000.00
    Ford Program Officer(s): Montes, Manuel F.; Funabiki, Jon
  - Trustees of Columbia University - Macroeconomics Task Force PA 10200276, 2004-2005 (Box 18, Folder 125, Box 19, Folder 126-127)
  - Center for Research, Support and Development of Culture PA 10501104, 2005-2008 (Box 19, Folder 128)
    Grantee: Center for Research, Support and Development of Culture
    Grant Dates: 2005 August 01-2009 January 31
    Grant Number: 10501104
    Grant Purpose: To collaborate with Hanoi Cultural University on a national curriculum in arts management that builds on existing degree programs and for a summer school at the Museum of Ethnology
    Grant Amount: $925,000.00; $925,000.00
    Ford Program Officer(s): DiGregorio, Michael R.
  - Manpower Demonstration Research Corporation (MDRC) PA 09800884, 2000-2005 (Box 20, Folder 129-130)
  - Stichting Centre on Housing Rights and Evictions PA 10100795, 2002-2003 (Box 20, Folder 131)
    Grantee: Stichting Centre on Housing Rights and Evictions
    Grant Dates: 2001 February 01-2010 February 28
    Grant Number: 10100795
    Grant Purpose: Support for projects in training, advocacy, and monitoring regarding forced evictions and housing rights
    Grant Amount: $1,215,000.00; $1,215,000.00
    Ford Program Officer(s): Cox, Larry; McCarthy, George W. (George William); Zard, Monette
  - Minnesota Council of Nonprofits PA 09701338, 1998-2001 (Box 21, Folder 132-133)
    Grantee: Minnesota Council of Nonprofits Inc.
    Grant Dates: 1997 August 01-2010 October 31
    Grant Number: 09701338
    Grant Purpose: Grants to state nonprofit associations for budget and tax analysis under an expansion of the state fiscal analysis initiative
    Grant Amount: $1,168,750.00; $1,168,750.00
    Ford Program Officer(s): Lipsky, Michael; Vaid, Urvashi; Edwards, Michael; McFate, Katherine
  - Manpower Demonstration Research Corporation (MDRC) PA 09800884, 2002-2003 (Box 21, Folder 134-135, Box 22, Folder 136-138)
  - Centre for Policy Studies PA 10300351, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 139)
    Grantee:Centre for Policy Studies
    Grant Dates:2003 January 01-2005 December 31
    Grant Number: 10300351
    Grant Purpose: For research, advocacy and networking to develop and monitor standards and indicators for peace and democratic governance in Africa
    Grant Amount:$350,000.00; $350,000.00
    Ford Program Officer(s): Aidoo, Akwasi
  - Youngstown State University PA 10001541, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 140)
    Grantee:Youngstown State University
    Grant Dates:2000 July 01-2007 August 31 Grant Number: 10001541
    Grant Purpose:Support for activities of the University's Center for Working Class Studies
    Grant Amount: $575,000.00; $575,000.00
    Ford Program Officer(s): Fraser, Gertrude Jacinta
  - University of Notre Dame Centre for Civil and Human Rights PA 10100797, 2003-2005 (Box 23, Folder 141-142)
    Grantee:The University of Notre Dame Du Lac
    Grant Dates:2001 May 01-2004 April 30
    Grant Number: 10100797
    Grant Purpose:Support for the University's Center for Civil and Human Rights to establish an Accountability Resource Center and conduct related activities
    Grant Amount: $750,000.00; $729,562.96
    Ford Program Officer(s): Cox, Larry
  - Social Science Research Council PA 09701051, 1998-2005 (Box 23, Folder 143, Box 24, Folder 144)
    Grantee:Social Science Research Council (SSRC)
    Grant Dates:1997 September 01-2006 September 30
    Grant Number: 09701051
    Grant Purpose:Support for awards program for sexuality research (950-1159)
    Grant Amount: $8,151,000.00; $8,151,000.00
    Ford Program Officer(s): Costa, Sarah Hawker; Klugman, Barbara
  - Centre for Science and Environment PA 10100421, 2002-2003 (Box 24, Folder 145-148)
    includes photographs
    Grantee: Centre for Science and Environment
    Grant Dates: 2001 January 15-2004 January 14
    Grant Number: 10100421
    Grant Purpose: Support for advocacy and public awareness campaigns on environmental justice aspects of water resources mgmt, small grants for community-based water harvesting systems, and an annual awards program
    Grant Amount: $350,000.00; $350,000.00
    Ford Program Officer(s): Pradhan, Ujjwal
  - Yayasan Penguatan dan Pemberdayaan Masyarakat (Eltayasa) PA 10100391, 2003-2004 (Box 25, Folder 149-150)
    Grantee: Yayasan Penguatan dan Pemberdayaan Masyarakat (Eltayasa)
    Grant Dates: 2001 January 01-2005 December 31
    Grant Number: 10100391
    Grant Purpose: Support to establish, assist and promote community forums and citizen charters in four cities in Sumatra
    Grant Amount: $250,000.00; $250,000.00
    Ford Program Officer(s): Antlov, Hans
  - National Immigration Forum PA 09801496, 1998-2001 (Box 25, Folder 151)
    Grantee: National Immigration Forum
    Grant Dates: 1998 June 01-2010 June 30
    Grant Number: 09801496
    Grant Purpose: Support for public-policy analysis, information sharing, public education, media outreach, advocacy, and alliance-building activities
    Grant Amount: $3,994,000.00; $3,994,000.00
    Ford Program Officer(s): Higashi, Taryn; Peters-Quintero, Mayra
  - Simon Wiesenthal Center, Inc. PA 10401097, 2002-2003 (Box 25, Folder 152)
    Grantee: Simon Wiesenthal Center
    Grant Dates: 2004 August 01-2006 July 31
    Grant Number: 10401097
    Grant Purpose: To design and conduct a tolerance & diversity training program for the New York State criminal justice community and determine the feasibility of developing a specialized version for U.N. personnel
    Grant Amount: $625,000.00; $625,000.00
    Ford Program Officer(s): Jenkins, Alan; Chiel, David
  - Harvard University PA 09701807, 2003-2005 (Box 25, Folder 153)
    Grant Dates: 1997 September 01-2006 June 30
    Grant Number: 09701807
    Grant Purpose: Support for community outreach and leadership training on issues of civil rights policy
    Grant Amount: $745,000.00; $745,000.00
    Ford Program Officer(s): Rios, Sara
  - Success for All Foundation, Inc. (10451326), 2003-2006 (Box 26, Folder 154)
    Grantee: Success for All Foundation, Inc.
    Grant Dates: 2004 September 15-2005 September 14
    Grant Number: 10451326
    Grant Purpose: To develop a strategic plan for targeting new markets for its school reform model
    Ford Program Officer(s): Petrovich, Janice
  - American Civil Liberties Union Foundation (ACLU) - Lesbian and Gay Rights Project (09901529), 1999-2001 (Box 26, Folder 155)
    Grantee: American Civil Liberties Union Foundation (ACLU)
    Grant Dates: 1999 August 01-2005 January 31
    Grant Number: 09901529
    Grant Purpose: Support for a project to address the needs of typically underserved members of the gay and lesbian community
    Grant Amount: $800,000.00; $800,000.00
    Ford Program Officer(s): Romero, Anthony D.; Jenkins, Alan; Winters, David
  - American Civil Liberties Union Foundation (ACLU) (10201529), 2002-2003 (Box 26, Folder 156)
    Grant Dates: 2002 June 01-2004 May 31
    Grant Number: 10201529
    Grant Purpose: Core support for the Security and Civil Liberties Task Force and for the Ira Glasser Fellows for Racial Justice program
    Grant Amount: $1,650,000.00; $1,650,000.00
    Ford Program Officer(s): Higashi, Taryn
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) Access Innovations for Digital Imaging Services (10190003), 2002 (Box 26, Folder 157)
    Grant Dates: 2001 January 01-2001 December 31
    Grant Number: 10190003
    Grant Purpose: Support for the design and pilot of an electronic library on the Foundation's Web site of Foundation publications currently available only in print
    Grant Amount: $200,000.00; $200,000.00
    Ford Program Officer(s): Feeney, Linda; Divack, Alan
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) Integra Dataware (10190003), 2002 (Box 27, Folder 158)
  - Casa Via Magia - V Mercado Cultural (09900720), 2003-2005 (Box 27, Folder 159)
    Grantee: Casa Via Magia
    Grant Dates: 1999 March 01-2005 February 28
    Grant Number: 09900720
    Grant Purpose: Tie-off support for the Center for Capacity Building and to produce the fifth and sixth Latin American Cultural Markets and conduct an independent evaluation
    Grant Amount: $3,845,000.00; $3,845,000.00
    Ford Program Officer(s): Pwono, Damien M.; Santos, John Phillip; Opoku-Mensah, Aida; Fraser, Gertrude Jacinta; Wilkerson, Margaret B. (Margaret Buford)
  - Center For Applied Linguistics - Interdisciplinary Committee on Reading Problems (06700554), 1971 February (Box 28, Folder 160-161)
    Grantee: Center For Applied Linguistics
    Grant Dates: 1967 September 01-1969 December 31
    Grant Number: 06700554
    Grant Purpose: Preparation of final reports of the interdisciplinary committee onreading problems
    Grant Amount: $151,297.00; $151,297.00
    Ford Program Officer(s): Martus, Marjorie
  - Radio Transcripts, Radio Reports, Inc. - Fulton Lewis, Jr. - Volume I, 1955 August 22-October 21 (Box 28, Folder 162)
  - Radio Transcripts, Radio Reports, Inc. - Fulton Lewis, Jr. - Volume II, 1955 October 14-1956 February 22 (Box 28, Folder 163)
  - Radio Transcripts, Radio Reports, Inc. - Fulton Lewis, Jr. - Volume III, 1956 February 23-1957 January 22 (Box 29, Folder 164)
  - Radio Transcripts, Radio Reports, Inc., 1956 January 2-November 3 (Box 29, Folder 165)
  - National Broadcasting Company #1270 - Image America Radio Transcripts - Program #1-16, The Fund for Adult Education (TFAE), 1960 (Box 29, Folder 166-168, Box 30, Folder 169-170)
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP) (07590003) - L. Filipopova (sp?) Moscow publication, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 171)
    Grant Dates: 1974 October 01-1977 September 30
    Grant Number: 07590003)
    Grant Purpose: Fiscal Years 1975 To 1977 Travel And Study Grants
    Grant Amount: $7,954,786.00; $7,954,786.00
  - Trustees Of The American School Of Classical Studies At Athens (07200175) - Publication by Lidia Martini, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 172)
    Grantee: Trustees Of The American School Of Classical Studies At Athens
    Grant Dates: 1972 June 01-1976 May 31
    Grant Number: 07200175
    Grant Purpose: Assistance in the publication of at least eight books of a byzantine and modern greek library
    Grant Amount: $43,500.00; $43,500.00
    Ford Program Officer(s): Sheldon, Richard C.
  - Company for the Development of Cinematography in Greece (07200082), 1972 (Box 30, Folder 173, Box 31, Folder 174)
    Grantee: Company for the Development of Cinematography in Greece
    Grant Dates: 1971 July 01-1973 June 30
    Grant Number: 07200082
    Grant Amount: $104,500.00; $104,500.00
    Ford Program Officer(s): Lowry, W. McNeil (Wilson McNeil)
  - University Of Agriculture (07450719) - Report on First National Workshop Extension Research and Evaluation by Alang Perang and Rahman Zainuddin, 1974 June 3-14 (Box 31, Folder 175)
    Grantee: University Of Agriculture
    Grant Dates: 1974 May 15-1974 July 14
    Grant Number: 07450719
    Grant Purpose: Support of first national workshop in extension evaluation and research at the university from June 3-14, 1974
    Grant Amount: $15,000.00; $7,500.00
    Ford Program Officer(s): Hathaway, Dale E.; Hungate, Jess
  - Public/Private Ventures (09301262) - Mentoring in the Juvenile Justice System: Findings from Two Pilot Programs, Crystal A. Mecartney, Melanie B. Styles, Kristine V. Morrow, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 176)
    Grantee: Public/private Ventures
    Grant Dates: 1993 August 01-1997 January 31
    Grant Number: 09301262
    Grant Purpose: Support for strengthening social infrastructure for successful teenage development and transition to adulthood.
    Grant Amount: $2,500,000.00; $2,500,000.00
    Ford Program Officer(s): Kubisch, Anne C.
  - Urbanization Policy and Political Development in Latin America by Robert T. Daland, 1968 April 23 (Box 31, Folder 177)
  - Manpower Demonstration Research Corporation (MDRC) (08700188) - Maryland: The Demonstration of State Work/Welfare Initiatives, Supplemental Report on the Baltimore Options Program, Daniel Friedlander, 1987 October (Box 31, Folder 178)
    Grant Dates: 1987 January 01-1988 August 31
    Grant Number: 08700188
    Grant Purpose: For pilot phase of project new chance aimed at helping young, welfare dependent mothers achieve economic self-sufficiency
    Ford Program Officer(s): Miller, Shelby H.
  - Tribal Research Centre (08050071) - Department of Public Welfare, Ministry of Interior, Chiang Mai, Thailand, Map of Center's Hillside, 1980 (Folder 396)
    Grantee: Tribal Research Centre
    Grant Dates: 1979 October 01-1980 September 30
    Grant Number: 08050071
    Grant Purpose: Partial support of publication of the centre's hilltribe map
    Grant Amount: $2,295.00; $2,295.00
    Ford Program Officer(s): Weldon, Peter D.
  - University of Washington (08000702) - Microfiche Catalog - East Asian Library, Serials Catalog for 1981 and Script Index (6 microfiche packet) (Box 31, Folder 179)
    Grantee: University of Washington
    Grant Dates: 1980 August 01-1981 October 31
    Grant Number: 08000702
    Grant Purpose: Computerization of catalog of east asian serials collection
    Grant Amount: $27,000.00; $27,000.00
    Ford Program Officer(s): Geithner, Peter F.
  - L71-30 - Self-Survey of Activities at Indiana University Under Ford Foundation Grants I (1961-71) and II (1966-71), 1971 (Box 32, Folder 180-183)
  - Southern Regional Council Inc. PA 09800953 - The New Latino South: An Introduction, 2001 December (Box 33, Folder 191)
    Grantee: Southern Regional Council
    Grant Dates: 1998 March 01-2006 May 31
    Grant Number: 09800953
    Grant Purpose: Support for anti-discrimination activities in the southern united states
    Grant Amount: $1,800,000.00; $1,800,000.00
  - Global Rights Advocacy Bridge Program PA 10300166 - Participation at the 60th Session of the UN Commission on Human Rights, 2004 March 22-April 2 (Box 34, Folder 192)
    Grantee: Global Rights
    Grant Dates: 2002 October 01-2010 June 30
    Grant Number: 10300166
    Grant Purpose: To build the capacity of human rights groups around the world
    Grant Amount: $3,050,000.00; $3,050,000.00
    Ford Program Officer(s): Cox, Larry; Rios, Sara; TBS/International Human Rights; Zard, Monette
  - Institute for Women's Policy Research PA 10400106 - The Ties That Bind: Women's Public Vision for Politics, Policy, and Civil Society, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 193)
    Grantee: Institute for Women's Policy Research
    Grant Dates: 2003 October 01-2008 October 31
    Grant Number: 10400106
    Grant Purpose: For research and public education on effective strategies for increasing women's civic involvement in both religious and secular social justice organizations
    Grant Amount: $850,000.00; $850,000.00
    Ford Program Officer(s): Buchanan, Constance H.
  - The Advancement Project PA 10300277 - Derailed! Media Report Advancement Project, 2004 February (Box 34, Folder 194)
    Grantee: The Advancement Project
    Grant Dates: 2002 December 01-2010 November 30
    Grant Number: 10300277
    Grant Purpose: General support for civil rights advocacy, communications, and technical assistance to community-based organizations on a range of race-related issues
    Ford Program Officer(s): Rios, Sara; Cox, Todd
  - National Partnership for Women and Families PA 09800934, 2001-2002 (Box 34, Folder 195-196)
    Grantee: National Partnership for Women and Families
    Grant Dates: 1998 April 01-2008 July 31
    Grant Number: 09800934
    Grant Purpose: Support for litigation, advocacy, policy research and related activities associated with the advancement of women
    Grant Amount: $3,810,000.00; $3,810,000.00
  - Social Science Research Council PA 09801197 - Board Retreat, 2001 January (Box 34, Folder 197)
  - Arms Control Association PA 10251135, 2003 (Box 34, Folder 198)
    Grantee: The Arms Control Association
    Grant Dates: 2002 April 01-2007 June 30
    Grant Number: 10251135
    Grant Purpose: To provide the media and others with information on arms control in the effort to stem the proliferation of weapons of mass destruction and other destabilizing weapons
    Grant Amount: $375,335.00; $375,335.00
    Ford Program Officer(s): Wing, Christine B.; Jenkins, Bonnie D.; Edwards, Michael
  - Creative Capital Foundation PA 10301353 - 2005 Grantee Handbook (Box 34, Folder 199)
    Grantee: Creative Capital Foundation
    Grant Dates: 2003 June 01-2010 May 31
    Grant Number: 10301353